For the development of the musculoskeletal system, and more specifically, what
Für die Entwicklung des Bewegungsapparates, und genauer gesagt, was
we are going to see now, are the vertebrae.
wir jetzt sehen werden, sind die Wirbel.
Do not forget that this segmentation is given.
Vergessen Sie nicht, dass es diese gegebene Segmentierung gibt.
We see that there will be trajectories for the axial skeleton, the ribs, and the extremities.
Wir sehen, dass es Bahnen für das Achsenskelett, die Rippen und die Extremitäten geben wird.
The skeleton, the consequence of the establishment of my notochord,
Das Skelett, die Folge der Anlage meiner Chorda dorsalis,
induces the establishment of what I call the neural tube.
induziert die Anlage dessen, was ich Neuralrohr nenne.
This neural tube
Dieses Neuralrohr
will gradually align itself along the longitudinal axis and organize the vascular system.
wird sich allmählich auf die Längsachse legen und das Gefäßsystem organisieren.
Retention field, the differential growth rate becomes anterior.
Retentionsfeld, die differentielle Wachstumsgeschwindigkeit wird anterior.
Behind, the movement does this.
Hinten macht die Bewegung dies.
So I have an aspiration field along the entire...
Ich habe also ein Saugfeld entlang des gesamten...
which happens like this, you see, that's where I have my segmentation.
das sich so bildet, sehen Sie, dort habe ich meine Segmentierung.
The anterior part will create what is called the ectodermal ring.
Der vordere Teil wird den sogenannten ektodermalen Ring bilden.
It's epiblast, okay?
Das ist Epiblast, okay?
It's a tissue that forms...
Das ist ein Gewebe, das...
all around like this, which is a ring in that direction,
ringsherum so, das ein Ring in dieser Richtung ist,
relative to me, and then it flexes like this.
im Verhältnis zu mir, und dann biegt es sich so.
And it is actually the flexion that creates this ring.
Und es ist tatsächlich die Biegung, die diesen Ring erzeugt.
So I have a tissue that is denser anteriorly.
Ich habe also ein Gewebe, das vorne dichter ist.
Thus, the consequences of the ventral curvature is the ectodermal ring.
Die Folgen der ventralen Krümmung sind also der ektodermale Ring.
And this ring will lead to a whole series of changes
Und dieser Ring wird eine ganze Reihe von Veränderungen mit sich bringen
with the curvature for the organism.
mit der Krümmung für den Organismus.
This flexion brings about the phase of embryonic delimitation.
Diese Biegung führt zur Abgrenzungsphase des Embryos.
Here I have my tube.
Hier habe ich mein Rohr.
I have my neural crests, not only is it there but it also does all of this and
Ich habe meine Neuralleisten, nicht nur ist er da, sondern er macht auch all dies und
it is this movement
es ist diese Bewegung
here of the ectodermal ring that will provide very important information
hier des ektodermalen Rings dort, die eine sehr wichtige Information geben wird
towards my noto
zu meiner Chorda
chord, so you see it's this compression and it does this and it comes like this I will find myself
dorsalis, Sie sehen also, es ist diese Kompression und es macht das und es kommt so, ich werde mich
find myself here with a movement that is induced towards my
hier mit einer Bewegung wiederfinden, die sich zu meiner
The notochord is the developmental movement.
Chorda dorsalis hin induziert, es ist die Entwicklungbewegung
here by this
hier durch diese
which forms a system around my notochord, which we will call the
die ein System um meine Chorda dorsalis bildet, das wir die
development of my intervertebral disc and the vertebral body.
Entwicklung meiner Bandscheibe und des Wirbelkörpers nennen werden.
This entire system will begin to separate; the superior part will form the disc
Dieses ganze System wird sich zu trennen beginnen, der obere Teil wird die Bandscheibe bilden
and the part below and above will begin to form the body.
und der untere und obere Teil wird beginnen, den Körper zu bilden.
But it is merely induced by my notochord and reorganized by, this time, the
Aber es wird nur durch meine Chorda dorsalis induziert und diesmal durch das
system of my neural crest, which is guided.
System meiner geführten Neuralleiste reorganisiert.
The notochord?
Die Chorda dorsalis?
it is the remnant and your nucleus pulposus; that way, it will give you context.
Das ist das Überbleibsel und dein Nucleus pulposus, so, das wird es dir verdeutlichen.
Initially, it is the same tissue.
Am Anfang ist es dasselbe Gewebe.
Initially, I have vascular information,
Am Anfang habe ich eine vaskuläre Information,
and afterwards, I have the metameric information from the neural crest.
und danach habe ich die metamerische Information der Neuralleiste.
So, you see, I have the neurological information.
Du siehst also, ich habe die neurologische Information.
And it is this neurological information that will separate the upper and lower parts
Und es ist diese neurologische Information, die den oberen und den unteren Teil trennen wird,
by molecular induction, which will lead to the formation of a disc.
durch molekulare Induktion, die dazu führen wird, dass ich eine Bandscheibe habe.
With the establishment of my notochord, we have the movement.
Platzierung meiner Notocorda, wir haben die Bewegung.
The induction that occurs around it, the nucleus pulposus will remain,
Die Induktion, die sich darum herum bildet, wird den Nucleus pulposus belassen,
it is the axis around which the sclerotome will form.
das ist die Achse, um die sich das Sklerotom aufbauen wird.
The notochord induces the formation of the vertebral bodies from the
Die Chorda induziert die Bildung der Wirbelkörper aus dem
sclerotome which originates from the somites.
Sklerotom, das von den Somiten stammt.
So that means that the notochord will induce the formation of the vertebral body
Das bedeutet also, dass die Notocorda die Bildung des Wirbelkörpers
and of the vertebral disc.
und der Bandscheibe induzieren wird.
Whereas everything around it, meaning the entire arch up to the spinous process,
Während alles, was sich darum herum befindet, also der gesamte Bogen bis zum Dornfortsatz,
That is induced by my notochord, and everything around here will be
Das wird durch meine Notocorda induziert, und alles, was sich hier darum herum befindet, wird
induced by my neural tube.
durch mein Neuralrohr induziert.
So, on a vertebra, two types of information.
Also, bei einem Wirbel, zwei Arten von Informationen.
If I consider the spinous process, I have direct information from my neural tube.
Wenn ich den Dornfortsatz nehme, habe ich eine direkte Information von meinem Neuralrohr.
If I consider the disc system, it is information about the notochord that induces the system.
Wenn ich zum Bandscheibensystem gehe, ist es eine Information über die Notocorda, die das System induziert.
The notochord will induce the formation of the vertebral bodies, which originates from the sclerotome,
Die Notocorda wird die Bildung der Wirbelkörper induzieren, die vom Sklerotom stammen,
while the neural tube will undergo formation.
während das Neuralrohr die Bildung formen wird.
from the surrounding mesoblast.
aus dem Mesoblast, der es umgeben wird.
Two different types of information.
Zwei verschiedene Arten von Informationen.
In the complete formation, there is the formation of my neural tube,
In der vollständigen Bildung habe ich die Bildung meines Neuralrohrs,
you see, by my notochord.
du siehst, durch meine Notocorda.
This will lead to a movement like this.
Das wird eine Bewegung wie diese hervorrufen.
We suddenly see all the so-called migration,
Wir sehen plötzlich die gesamte Migration, in Anführungszeichen,
the arrangement of the somites to form my sclerotome
die Platzierung der Somiten, um mein Sklerotom zu bilden
around the neural tube and around my notochord.
um das Neuralrohr und um meine Notocorda herum.
Two types of information.
Zwei Arten von Informationen.
Here, it will be essential.
Hier wird das wesentlich sein.
Specifically, the sclerotome to form the vertebral body; here, we will say it is a type of sclerotome
Insbesondere das Sklerotom zur Bildung des Wirbelkörpers, hier werden wir sagen, dass es eine Form von Sklerotom
of mesoblastic type to form the vertebral arch and the spinous process.
mesoblastischen Typs ist, um den Wirbelbogen und den Dornfortsatz zu bilden.
If you consider this, either you position yourself relative to your neural tube, and then we will have
Wenn Sie hier nehmen, entweder Sie beziehen sich auf Ihr Neuralrohr, und dort werde ich
the formation of my entire arch,
die Bildung meines gesamten Bogens haben,
or I will position myself relative to my central notochordal line,
oder ich werde mich auf meine zentrale Notocorda-Linie beziehen,
and I will have the vertebral body.
und ich werde den Wirbelkörper haben.
One on the longitudinal plane, the other on the transverse plane.
Die eine auf der Längsebene, die andere auf der Querebene.
We see the entire movement here.
Wir sehen die ganze Bewegung hier.
And here, we still have this vertebral body that will form differently,
Und hier haben wir noch diesen Wirbelkörper, der sich anders bilden wird,
with yet another important level, which will be the neural crest level.
avec encore un autre niveau important qui sera le niveau de la crête neurale.
This, we will do in practice; it's how we will palpate the body.
Ça, on va faire dans la pratique, c'est comment on va toucher le corps.
We will position ourselves either at the level purely of the neural tube to form this entire posterior arch,
On va se mettre soit sur le niveau purement du tube neural pour former tout cet arc postérieur,
or we will position ourselves on the longitudinal axis to work on the vertebral body,
soit on se mettra sur l'axe longitudinal pour travailler le corps vertébral,
or we will place ourselves in another plane to work on the migration of the neural crest.
ou bien on va se remettre dans un autre plan pour travailler la migration de la crête neurale.
The entire vertebra is being outlined simultaneously.
J'ai tout le vertèbre qui se dessine en même temps.
On top of that, there is the skin, there is the neural tube, and there is my notochord.
Là-dessus, il y a la peau, il y a le tube neural et il y a ma notte-corte.
Each one, I send out small molecules.
Chacun, j'envoie des petites molécules.
I am the notochord; I will be responsible for forming the vertebra.
Moi, je suis la notte-corte, moi je vais m'occuper pour former la vertèbre.
Bring me the material.
Amène-moi le matos.
At the level of the neural tube, I will initiate inductions,
Au niveau du tube neural, ok, moi je vais donner, je vais prendre, je te donne des inductions,
I will be responsible for forming the vertebral arch and spinous process.
moi je vais m'occuper pour former l'arc et l'épineuse.
And then, once this is established, where ossification begins,
Et puis au moment où j'ai ça, où ça commence à s'ensifier,
thereupon,
là-dessus,
this then provides the specific induction for my neural tube
d 'un  coup  ça  donne  l 'induction  spécifique  pour  mon  tube
and to state, 'Okay, I will now initiate'
neural  et  dire  ok  moi  maintenant  je  lance
the entire program for my nerves to ultimately form what are known as dermatomes,
tout  le  programme  pour  mes  nerfs  pour  former  finalement  ce  qu 'on  appelle  les  dermatomes
which
qui
will be segmented throughout the body, associated with what are termed dermalgias. If
seront  segmentés  sur  tout  le  corps  avec  ce  qu 'on  appelle  des  dermalgies  si
you present with a dermalgia on
tu  as  une  dermalgie  sur
a dermatome, the corresponding viscus should be examined. If multiple dermalgias are present
un dermatome il fallait voir le viscère si tu as plusieurs dermalgies
on a single dermatome, one must consider examining the corresponding vertebra.
sur  un  même  dermatome  il  faut  penser  à  aller  voir  la  vertèbre
For instance, here in dermalgia 9, I
par  exemple  ici  dans  la  dermalgie  9  je
observe within this dermalgia a positive skin rolling test, and a densification that
me  retrouve  ici  avec  dans  cette  dermalgie  un  palpé  roulé  et  là  j 'ai  une  densification  qui
appears, corresponding to the gallbladder. Proceeding, I note another one here that
apparaît  qui  correspond  à  la  vésicule  biliaire  j 'avance  tiens  j 'ai  une  autre  ici  qui
corresponds
correspond
to the pancreas, which is also indurated, and centrally, I identify what is termed the pyloric system.
au  pancréas  aussi  qui  a  duré  et  au  centre  j 'ai  ce  qu 'on  appelle  le  système  pylorique
If I have all
j 'ai  les
three manifesting during my palpation,
trois qui apparaissent dans mon palpé
I would then prioritize examining the corresponding vertebra.
je vais aller voir plutôt ma vertèbre.
If only one distinct manifestation appears,
Si j'en ai une qui apparaisse, bien nette,
I will consider examining the organ.
je vais penser à aller voir l'organe.